[
    {
        "front": "だま",
        "back": "(Suffix for Coin/s)",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "さつ",
        "back": "(Suddix for Note/s)",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "いくら",
        "back": "How much",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "かばん",
        "back": "Bag",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "バイキ",
        "back": "Bike",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "くるま",
        "back": "Car",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "けいたい でんわ, すまほん",
        "back": "Cell Phone, Smart Phone",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぱそこん",
        "back": "Laptop, Computer",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "とけい",
        "back": "Watch/Clock",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "うで とけい",
        "back": "Wrist Watch",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "いす",
        "back": "Chair",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "つくえ",
        "back": "Table",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "いえ",
        "back": "House",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "ペン",
        "back": "Pen",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "くつ",
        "back": "Shoes",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちょっと",
        "back": "Little bit",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "とても",
        "back": "Very",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "ドル",
        "back": "Dollar",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "やすみ",
        "back": "Holiday, Break",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "きゅうじつ",
        "back": "National Holiday",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "きゅけい",
        "back": "Break",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "なつ やすみ",
        "back": "Summer Break",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "がっこう",
        "back": "School",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "かばん",
        "back": "Bag",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぱそこん",
        "back": "Computer",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "おちゃ",
        "back": "(Green) Tea",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "おさけ",
        "back": "Alcohol",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "しごと",
        "back": "Work/Job",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "せき",
        "back": "Seat",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "しんぶん",
        "back": "Newspaper",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "ビル",
        "back": "Building",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "ビール",
        "back": "Bear",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゅくだい",
        "back": "Homework",
        "chapter": "N5 C2"
    }
]